<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>🦝 Gambits &amp; Exploits</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on 🦝 Gambits &amp; Exploits</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:20:31 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enforce uniform code formatting across teams</title><link>/posts/uniform-code-formatting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:20:31 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/uniform-code-formatting/</guid><description>Enforce uniform code formatting across teams Link to heading With the rise of language centric formatting tools like gofmt, it&amp;rsquo;s become easier than ever to achieve a holistic coding style across team members and projects, avoiding endless warfare over primeval subjective matters like white space after punctuation, tabs vs. Spaces, etc&amp;hellip; It also combats the cargo cult around style guides promoted by large tech companies (such as the AirBnB JS Guide) - although these are still around, they&amp;rsquo;ve become much more focused on overall code architecture and idiomatic usage of their governed language.</description></item><item><title/><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Gambits and exploits in software engineering Link to heading More like my personal 🧠 dump really &amp;hellip; I keep forgetting things, so I decided to start writing some of it down in a constructive manner. Maybe some of it might proof interesting to you.
This blog is open source and available at github. Feel free to reach out in case you have any questions, submit Pull Requests or simply fork and use for your own pleasure.</description></item><item><title/><link>/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/</guid><description>Some of the projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been professionally involved with Link to heading Respiratory Diagnostics, real time measuring, data processing, hardware protocol design, hardware prototyping, reporting and more. Automatic loading and Smart Factory solutions, reaching from real time robotics and human security safeguard constraints to process automation, job scheduling and monitoring. Teach Online, a greenfield, globally distributed learning platform for teaching English around the world. ValutaChange, a greenfield startup project, opening up brand new markets for reward tokens and loyalty programs.</description></item></channel></rss>